[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mars lower density and size gives it a mass about how much that of Earth?", "correct_answer": "1/10", "incorrect_answers": ["1/6", "1/8", "1/2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the length of the 2007 movie Ghost Rider?", "correct_answer": "114 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["122 minutes", "91 minutes", "100 minutes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Will two tectonic plates sliding away from each other result in an earthquake?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What anniversary was Gotham celebrating in the 1989 film Batman?", "correct_answer": "200th", "incorrect_answers": ["75th", "250th", "100th"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the biggest artery in the human body?", "correct_answer": "aorta", "incorrect_answers": ["umbilical", "pulmonary", "systemic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Menomonee Valley along the Menomonee River in Milwaukee, Wisconsin has what peculiar shape?", "correct_answer": "U-shape", "incorrect_answers": ["S-shape", "Y-shape", "V-shape"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Al the languages of Europe, except three, are derived from Indian languages, probably Sanskrit or Tamil. Which three are the exceptions?", "correct_answer": "Hungarian, Estonian, and Finnish", "incorrect_answers": ["Norwegian, Danish, and Swedish", "Andorran, Catalan, and Provencal", "Romanian, Romansch, and English"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this year, Led  Zeppelin  released Stairway to Heaven and  Andrew Lloyd Webbers Jesus Christ Superstar opened.", "correct_answer": "1971", "incorrect_answers": ["1977", "1973", "1975"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year were pencils first mass-produced?", "correct_answer": "1662 A.D.", "incorrect_answers": ["476 A.D.", "1812 A.D.", "1821 A.D."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2006, a crocodile housed at the Australia Zoo, was estimated to be 130 years old.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie Scarface, Tony goes back to Cuba.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these colors do sapphires come?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "Blue", "Green"]}]